Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is a time known as
the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide.
Raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Until someone proves it real.
Through it all.
Through all the trouble of times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there.
To stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
You've raised your prices again?
That's a little steep, don't you think?
Raise your prices again
and I'll stop paying.
What's the big deal?
It's just one paper.
Just one paper?
I buy these every day.
Yeah,
but there's no need to
save every last berry
so you can buy back your
village from Arlong,
you know?
You can finally stop
obsessing about money.
You're so stupid.
Now that all that stuff's over,
I'm saving money for me now.
Jeez, I'm not gonna be one of those poor
pirates who can't even afford to dress up.
Whoa, calm down.
I'm in the middle of developing
my special Tabasco star.
An eye full of this
will make any bad guy...
Oh, come on!
I just want one of them!
No!
This is Nami's tangerine orchard!
I won't let anyone lay a finger on it!
Nami, can you see how well
I'm protecting your trees?
Yes, you're doing very well.
Oh, Sanji's getting
used, that poor bastard.
I only want one tangerine.
Just give it here.
You're so mean.
No!
Oh, well.
I'm pretty happy anyway.
The world's sure a turbulent place.
They just had another coup in Villa.
What's that?
Huh?
Ah! Ah!
Uh! Huh?
Ah!
So,
even a conservative
estimate of their power
says they're too much for
our branches to handle?
That's right.
Even before forming his pirate group,
he defeated Marine Branch
Captain Axe Hand Morgan,
which he did single-handedly.
And since then, he's showed
no signs of slowing down.
Buggy the Clown, 15 million.
Pirate Fleet Commodore
Don Krieg, 17 million.
Fishman Pirate Sawtooth,
Arlong, 20 million.
These pirates were big players, and they
had bounties of over 10 million berries.
By comparison, the average
bounty is only 3 million berries.
He took them down.
It's true that 30 million berries as a
starting bounty is globally unprecedented.
But in my opinion, it's necessary.
It's best to destroy such
seeds of villainy early on,
before they've had a
chance to get out of hand.
Absolutely.
All right, guys, we're wanted criminals!
That's a whole lot of fairies!
Check it out!
I'll be seen all around the world!
These girls might even fall for you!
What?
They put Long Nose in but left me out?
Where are you?
I don't see you anywhere.
You're not there.
It's the back of your head.
That's not so great.
Aw, don't be so glum.
You don't have to be a captain to get
your picture on one of these things.
Huh? Is that true?
Yeah, just work really hard.
Let's go to the Grand Line, men!
Yet again, you guys don't understand
how grim our situation really is.
This means all of our lives
will be in constant danger.
Okay, this is no time to be
relaxing in the East Blue.
30 million berries.
At that amount, I bet
headquarters will take action!
Not to mention there'll be
bounty hunters to deal with.
And with this kind of
bounty, they'll be good.
Miss?
Miss Kaya!
Miss, it's amazing!
Mary, what's wrong?
Have you seen this, flyer?
Look, it's Usopp!
See, that's definitely
Usopp facing the other way!
Hey, you know what?
You're right.
Finally!
Luffy, you're finally living your dream!
I'm Monkey D.
Luffy, and I'm gonna
be king of the pirates!
See ya!
But if we meet again,
we will meet as enemies.
We're getting closer.
We've almost made it to the Grand Line.
There's a famous city on this
island known as Loguetown.
Loguetown?
I'm pretty sure I've heard of it before.
It's the city of the
beginning and the end.
It's the town where the old
King of the Pirates, Gold Roger,
was both born and killed.
That's where the King of the Pirates died.
Well?
Yeah, let's do it.
This was the man who had the One Piece.
Everything the world has to offer, I need
to see where he was born and executed.
If you wish to flee, then do so now.
We owe the passion of peace in this
world, and weakness will not be tolerated.
The feeble public counts on us.
We alone are the righteous ones.
If there is evil on the
seas, then we, the Marines,
must drive it away with
the utmost prejudice.
In the name of absolute peace!
Yes, sir!
Woo-hoo!
This is going to be so fun!
Every pirate headed to the Grand
Line stops here to resupply.
It has everything you could possibly need.
If that's the case, then I'm
going to go on a shopping spree.
I'll bet they have all
sorts of stuff here.
I'll be able to stock up on fresh produce.
And fresh women.
You'd think there'd be a
swordsmith around here.
I thought you were broke.
Are you going to steal a sword?
Well, I'm going to find
out where they kill people.
Huh?
I've got to see where the King
of the Pirates was executed.
Hey, wait!
We have to pick a meeting place!
Oh, that's not good.
The King of the Pirates was
born and executed in this town.
I could be running in his very
footsteps right now. Yahoo!
These swords are all
so freaking expensive.
Sure, I'll lend you some money.
That'll just be 300 % interest.
I can't afford to borrow any
more money from that girl.
But I can't go to the grand
line stuck with just one sword.
There's got to be a way.
Monster, how rude.
Shut up.
Our boss is behind bars
because of you and your
idiot of a captain Haven't
you learned your lesson?
Definitely not.
Guess we need you to teach us again!
We're supposed to bring your corpse to our
boss so he can see that
we finished you off.
If you insist, I will fight you!
She's really very funny.
You do know you're a girl, right?
Oh, she did it that was awesome
She's good with a sword,
but not so good at walking.
Oh, man.
Where are they?
Hey, here you go.
Thanks.
That's so kind.
May I have my glasses?
How do I look?
You look absolutely engaging. And now...
Artistically extravagant. This?
Considuously elevated, acrimoniously
alteraged, artificially executed,
may I deliver these to your lodgings?
No thanks, a little too
expensive for my taste.
Thank you, come back soon!
Ah, a perfect aperitif.
Coupled with two
mouth-watering delicacies?
Oh, with so much on the menu,
I can't decide where to start.
Oh, I wish this was a buffet.
Whoa, I think I just
found the main course!
Whoa, crazy!
I think I've died and
gone to trinket heaven!
Come in, come in!
In our humble store,
almost everything you see?
Is a near priceless pirate artifact.
from Adventure to the Grand Line.
I am certain you will not find a
store like this in the entire world.
So then, everything in this store
has been to the Grand Line and back?
Is that what you're telling me?
You are so observant.
We only accept a certain type of clientele
in this establishment, you might imagine.
And I can tell by your demeanor
that you're my type of client.
Observe!
I hold in my hands a gun that was once the
favorite of none other than
THE Gold Roger! No way!
Gold Roger's gun? Yes.
Just breathe, sir.
There's more to come.
Show me everything! Right this way!
Wait hold on excuse me
where are we going i
still can't believe that
you broke my glasses.
I told you i'll pay you
back okay jeez you'll pay
me back you don't look
like you have any money.
Am i right well that's
true i am kind of broke
i knew it i can tell by
the look on your face.
that you're pretty desperate.
What is it?
Your sick mother needs medicine?
Or did your wife run
away with another man?
And leave you all alone?
to raise the children by yourself?
Hey, hold on.
Don't explain.
Just come with me.
Marines.
Here.
Once you start working for the
Marines, you'll never have to worry?
about money problems ever again.
Not a chance in hell.
I don't work for Marines.
You can't leave now!
I expect to be paid back for my glasses.
Ah, crap.
Sergeant Major, it's time for training.
I'll be back to check on you.
She's a sergeant?
Crap, this is gonna
take the whole damn day!
Unless...
Three mop technique work like a charm.
One more time!
Hey, you!
Just what do you think you're doing?
Huh?
It's Zoro, the pirate hunter.
Why are you cleaning?
Intel says you've teamed up with Monkey D.
Luffy's crew.
Drop the mop!
Huh?
Guess I should leave.
What happened here?
They appear to have been attacked, but
there's no sign of who's responsible.
New glasses.
Man, that was just too weird.
She looked just like Kuina.
Not to mention she was a
swordsman of all things.
A crazy world.
I doubt I'll ever see her again.
I'd like to pick up some swords.
Of course, of course. Welcome.
Have a look at anything you'd like.
We have an extremely large
variety to choose from.
I've got 100,000 berries for
two swords. Can you do that?
Two for 100,000?
Great.
This guy is broke.
For $50,000 apiece, I can only
give you two dollar blades.
I can make do with whatever.
I just don't have the money right now.
You can't make do with whatever
unless you're an amateur.
Wait!
That sword! Could it be?
No, no, no, hold on a second.
I just want to take a look
at that sword you got there.
Is that okay with you, pal?
You okay there, buddy?
Let me see! Yeah, whatever.
This is really it!
Stay cool!
Poker face!
A complete amateur just walked
in with a legendary sword.
It's showtime!
Wow, that's a pretty nice sword you got.
You want to sell it?
I'll give you 200,000 berries for it.
What do you say?
That will leave you with 300,000, which
should buy you some pretty good steel.
At $100,000 a piece, there are bound
to be three swords you like in here.
What?
Are you kidding me? All right.
I'll give you $250,000 berries. No, wait.
$300,000.
Buy the law for $500,000. Just stop.
I'm not selling.
The sword is mine. Tough guy!
I'll buy it from you for $650,000 berries!
Okay, fine. I give up.
How does $800,000 berries sound to you?
I'm back!
Did you finish polishing my shigure?
You're okay.
I was worried about you.
See, some marines were
attacked earlier, right?
By where you had been mopping
the floors, you were gone though,
so naturally I just assumed
that you had been kidnapped.
Thank goodness.
She's not very bright.
The fact that you're here means
you must have run away. Sad.
You really must have no idea how to
accept love when it comes your way.
Do you?
So here's your stupid money back.
I don't need it.
I can't accept money from
a heartless and great.
Besides, look, I already
got some new glasses.
That sword looks just
like the Wado Ichimonji.
Is this really the sword?
Wado?
Stop talking! Stop talking!
It's beautiful!
This has to be one of
the 21-O-Wazamono swords.
See? Look at this.
It says here that this sword is worth
no less than 10 million berries.
But you're broke.
How do you have this legendary sword?
Damn!
You just had to keep talking, didn't you?
I'm going to sue your ass
for obstruction of business.
Obstruction of business?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what I did,
but please forgive me.
Here, I've finished polishing
your precious shigure for you.
Now just take it and get out.
I don't want to see you in my store again.
Just get out before you
tear my store apart!
I'm so sorry.
Did she ever help you dodge a bullet?
It is a complete waste to
have such a legendary sword
attached to someone who has
no idea of its true value.
You could pick from our lovely selection
of barrel swords for $50,000 apiece.
Pick any two you like.
What is that guy's problem?
You must lose a lot of swords if you think
you have to carry three of them around.
Unless, of course, you're like
that famous pirate hunter.
Pirate hunter, yeah.
He's quite the legend.
His name is Roronoa.
Oh, yeah, him. Yeah,
he's known throughout the East
Blue for his amazing sword skills,
but he's not a good person.
A swordsman who is just a bounty hunter
is no honorable swordsman at all.
Everything's backwards.
It's really too bad for real swordsmen.
Pirates and bounty hunters as swordmasters,
it just doesn't make any sense.
They have most of the world's
legendary swords, too.
It's a real tragedy.
I don't know.
It's the kind of thing you have to look
at on a case-by-case basis, I guess.
You never know what people are capable of.
This is my Shigure.
I'm going to work as hard as
I can to perfect my skills,
and then one day I'll take
back all the legendary swords?
because the filthy hands that hold
them now have no right to wield them.
Yes, the 21 top Owazumonos, the 21
Owazumonos, as well as the Ryo-Wazumonos.
I'll find them all.
And this one, my sword,
the Wado Ichimonji.
uh i'm not trying to get the legendary
swords back for my sake i just
don't want criminals to have them
this
sword is i
think that's let's see
just as i thought kitetsu kitetsu the
third its predecessor kitetsu the second is
an owazumono And Kitetsu the first before
that is listed as a top Owazumono sword.
Hey, are you really only selling
this one for 50,000 berries? Yeah.
Unbelievable.
That's an authentic Wazumono.
Wow, you have to buy that sword.
It's worth at least a
million berries or more.
You can't pass it up.
It's too valuable.
Damn it.
I can't sell it.
I didn't think so.
I knew there must have been some mistake.
This is a legendary sword.
It's not what you think.
The swords cursed how
do you know just do the
Kitetsu swords are
superior in all respects?
But they've been cursed
since their beginnings
you have to believe me there are stories
from All over a master
swordsman Who have met
their death after taking
up a Kitetsu sword.
Nobody is stupid enough to
even touch them these days.
And you'll fall to its curse as
well if you decide to take it.
I'm scared to let you buy it.
I'm afraid it'll curse me too.
Just leave it alone.
How horrible.
I'm sorry I even brought it up.
It would be death to take that sword.
Sounds great.
Think I'll take it.
I can't sell it, You fool!
Because if something happens
to you with that sword,
the curse could come back to me?
Don't be an idiot.
Let him buy that sword.
You old fool.
Don't hit me.
Well, we'll see
How about we find out which one is
stronger the swords curse or my good luck?
Stop it you're gonna chop
your arm off you fool
I'll take it.
Hey, pick out another.
Uh, okay. You! Wait here!
It is covered in a black lacquer finish
with an uneven temper pattern.
My shop is small, but this
is the finest sword I have.
It is named the Rio Azamono Yubashiri.
I told you.
I'm flat broke. It's too much. No matter.
I'll give it to you free of
charge if you'll take it.
You're welcome to the Kitetsu as well.
You deserve it.
Haven't run across a real
swordsman in a while.
I'm sorry I tried to cheat you before.
You must have some damn good luck, friend.
I definitely feel better
having three swords again.
What the hell?
You can't buy me anything nice, but
you can give away our best sword.
That sword belongs in the
hands of a true swordsman.
here why don't you take out the garbage
yes ma 'am that's weird who was that guy
what's that yeah let me see
Why are you here?
Answer me, Hawkeye?
Just calm down.
Where is your leader?
My business is with him.
Camping out on an island.
What a carefree man!
Boss!
Ah!
H-H-H-H-HawkEye!
Hey there, Hawkeye.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Have you come to fight me?
Because, you know, I'm not
feeling so good at the moment.
Now that you've lost your left arm.
I have no intention of settling the score!
I recently found an interesting pirate.
Seeing him reminded me of
a story you used to tell.
A story about a boy.
A strange boy from a small village.
Ha, ha, Luffy, you made it.
All right then, Hawkeye, in that case.
I'm afraid I can't let
you just leave. Not now.
Hawkeye! Drink them!
Go on, till they're back!
It's a celebration!
Weren't you hungover?
Oh, no way! Not anymore!
Drink, drink, drink!
Drink it!
That's it!
Everybody!
Let's get drunk!
Yeah, but wait, boss!
I thought you said you felt like crap
because you drank too much last night!
Don't be stupid!
I can't not drink on a
joyous day like today!
But the sun is still hot.
Don't sweat it.
Time to party.
Did you hear the news?
Luffy's a wanted man now.
Good for him.
Well, I'll be.
A great pirate came from
our tiny little village.
Yeah, who would have thought?
Shut up, you boneheads. Mr. Mayor?
What's so great about some Newgate
criminal coming from our little village?
To Luffy.
Bunch of jerks.
All of them.
Just look at him, Mayor.
He looks so happy.
A pirate's a pirate.
I will make it as a pirate, and
then I'll be king of the pirates.
You see, Luffy's achieved his dream.
Hasn't he?
His dream
of fate.
Thank you.